<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="pt-BR" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal.atom"/>
  <title>Testament - Genesis - Journal</title>
  <updated>2020-12-21T13:30:00-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Testament - Genesis</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal/11748285-a-tiled-blog-post</id>
    <published>2020-12-21T13:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-05T15:08:00-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal/11748285-a-tiled-blog-post"/>
    <title>The launch party</title>
    <author>
      <name>Richard Bairstow</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>You asked, we listened. Say hello to our new and improved website that will make us your favorite online shopping destination.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal/11748285-a-tiled-blog-post">Mais</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">We are pleased to offer you our latest website and online shopping experience.</p>
<p>So it has been a lengthy process but we are finally here.<br><br>We had a blast launching and know that those of you who could attend really enjoyed yourself.<br><br>Over the past months, we know you have put up with us asking questions about your shopping habits, answered surveys about where else you like to buy and what you like and dislike about our website. Well, we listened and think that we came up with something perfect that will make us your favorite online shopping destination.<br><br>We don't want to bore you with all of the details but it is a complete overhaul from top to bottom, gone are those annoying little glitches and delays. In their place is a sleek, fast and efficient experience targetted to help you find what you are looking for as we know that many of you are sometimes in a hurry.<br><br>Of course, this wouldn't be possible without the help of our fantastic theme development and support team who helped us along the way. We just hope that as our customers you will get the same great level of service from us.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal/11748281-a-new-article</id>
    <published>2020-12-17T13:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-02-06T12:16:54-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal/11748281-a-new-article"/>
    <title>Laundry personalities</title>
    <author>
      <name>Richard Bairstow</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span>Recognizing </span><span xml:lang="EN-US">your laundry personality and choosing products that cater to your unique style<span> </span>will make doing laundry an easy and enjoyable<span> </span>affair.</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal/11748281-a-new-article">Mais</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div>
<p><br>(BPT) - <span xml:lang="EN-US"><span xml:lang="EN-US">Chic, trendy, sporty, bohemian, sophisticated, fun, classic <span xml:lang="EN-US">—<span xml:lang="EN-US"> you probably have a clear vision of <span xml:lang="EN-US">your fashion and <span xml:lang="EN-US">style<span xml:lang="EN-US"> personality<span xml:lang="EN-US">. But do you know your laundry personality? How you wash the clothes you wear is every bit as personal and unique to you as the clothes themselves. Knowing your laundry personality could <span xml:lang="EN-US">help ease the load<span xml:lang="EN-US"> and <span xml:lang="EN-US">make the chore easy and fail-proof.</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">A <span xml:lang="EN-US">quarter of American households say they <span xml:lang="EN-US">overload their washer most of the time<span xml:lang="EN-US">, <span xml:lang="EN-US">according to <span xml:lang="EN-US">a survey commissioned by LG Electronics<span xml:lang="EN-US">.<span xml:lang="EN-US"> <span xml:lang="EN-US">Even people who say they<span xml:lang="EN-US"> are <span xml:lang="EN-US">doing their laundry efficiently <span xml:lang="EN-US">still<span xml:lang="EN-US"> have complaints with the process<span xml:lang="EN-US">.<span xml:lang="EN-US"> In fact, more than <span xml:lang="EN-US">three-fourths believe washers can be improved. </span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">Recognizing <span xml:lang="EN-US">your laundry personality and choosing products that cater to your unique style <span xml:lang="EN-US">will make doing laundry an easy, <span xml:lang="EN-US">and perhaps even enjoyable, <span xml:lang="EN-US">affair!<span xml:lang="EN-US"> Here are <span xml:lang="EN-US">four<span xml:lang="EN-US"> <span xml:lang="EN-US">common laundry personalities, their identifying traits, and tips for achieving maximum efficiency: </span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><strong><span xml:lang="EN-US">The light loader </span></strong></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">Does your desire to separate and preserve clothes, including those delicate special care <span xml:lang="EN-US">items,<span xml:lang="EN-US"> ever leave you with the only option of running the washer with just one or two items? You’re not alone. <span xml:lang="EN-US">According to a recent survey commissioned by LG Electronics, <span xml:lang="EN-US">60 percent of Americans admitted to running a full load of laundry for six items or less. </span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">The <a href="http://www.lg.com/us/twinwash" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span xml:lang="EN-US">LG <span xml:lang="EN-US">TWINWash<span xml:lang="EN-US"><span xml:lang="EN-US"> system</span></span></span></span></a><span xml:lang="EN-US"> will<span xml:lang="EN-US"> put an end to that, <span xml:lang="EN-US">let<span xml:lang="EN-US">ting<span xml:lang="EN-US"> consumers tackle two loads of <span xml:lang="EN-US">laundry<span xml:lang="EN-US"> at once, or independently<span xml:lang="EN-US">. The industry-first two-in-one washing machine includes <span xml:lang="EN-US">a front-load washer ergonomically placed on the top for larger loads, and a smaller washer, the LG Sidekick, which sits within the pedestal for those small specialty loads. The LG <span xml:lang="EN-US">SideKick<span xml:lang="EN-US"> provides an additional 1-foot capacity and has six cycles to choose from: normal, intimates, hand wash, active wear, rinse + spin and tub clean, allowing consumers to wash those smaller loads, saving time and energy. </span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><strong><span xml:lang="EN-US">The super sorter </span></strong></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">Does the thought of washing dark jeans and a pink blouse in the same loa<span xml:lang="EN-US">d leave you light-headed? You and <span xml:lang="EN-US">20<span xml:lang="EN-US"> percent of Americans <span xml:lang="EN-US">prefer to avoid mixing items of different colors in the same load. Some <span xml:lang="EN-US">of those surveyed <span xml:lang="EN-US">also <span xml:lang="EN-US">don’t <span xml:lang="EN-US">trust washing<span xml:lang="EN-US"> items like delicates (52<span xml:lang="EN-US"> percent), <span xml:lang="EN-US">jackets (49<span xml:lang="EN-US"> pe<span xml:lang="EN-US">r<span xml:lang="EN-US">cent) and <span xml:lang="EN-US">blouses (30<span xml:lang="EN-US"> percent) <span xml:lang="EN-US">in the main wash<span xml:lang="EN-US">. </span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">Facilitate your separation efforts by using multiple baskets or hampers in your laundry room. Label them <span xml:lang="EN-US">—<span xml:lang="EN-US"> darks, whites, delicates, workout, etc. <span xml:lang="EN-US">—<span xml:lang="EN-US"> and encourage family members to drop their dirty clothes in the appropriate basket. <span xml:lang="EN-US">For items not trusted for the main wash, the LG <span xml:lang="EN-US">SideKick<span xml:lang="EN-US">, part of the <span xml:lang="EN-US">TWINWash<span xml:lang="EN-US"> <span xml:lang="EN-US">system,<span xml:lang="EN-US"> can help tackle smaller loads<span xml:lang="EN-US">, ensuring they’re properly washed by one of the six cycles<span xml:lang="EN-US">.</span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>
<div>
<div>
<p><strong><span xml:lang="EN-US">The dumper </span></strong></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">Do you do minimal separation?<span xml:lang="EN-US"> <span xml:lang="EN-US">You’re <span xml:lang="EN-US">joined by a majority of Americans that load up their washer. A<span xml:lang="EN-US"> recent survey<span xml:lang="EN-US"> concluded that<span xml:lang="EN-US"> 80 percent <span xml:lang="EN-US">of Americans have<span xml:lang="EN-US"> purposely overloaded their washer to avoid doing a second load of laundry.<span xml:lang="EN-US"> Plus,<span xml:lang="EN-US"> 22 percent of Americans have deemed clothes not properly cleaned because of an overloaded washer. <span xml:lang="EN-US">High-efficiency front-load washing machines<span xml:lang="EN-US"> alleviate <span xml:lang="EN-US">both <span xml:lang="EN-US">of <span xml:lang="EN-US">these problem<span xml:lang="EN-US">s<span xml:lang="EN-US">. <span xml:lang="EN-US">Unlike traditional top-load washing machines with agitators, f<span xml:lang="EN-US">ront-load washers<span xml:lang="EN-US"> offer greater capacity while<span xml:lang="EN-US"> us<span xml:lang="EN-US">ing<span xml:lang="EN-US"> <span xml:lang="EN-US">much <span xml:lang="EN-US">less water<span xml:lang="EN-US">, which actually cleans clothes better! It’s a myth that more water equals cleaner clothes. Plus, they <span xml:lang="EN-US">have <span xml:lang="EN-US">f<span xml:lang="EN-US">aster spin<span xml:lang="EN-US"> speeds than their top-load counterparts,<span xml:lang="EN-US"> which <span xml:lang="EN-US">means<span xml:lang="EN-US"> your clothes come out <span xml:lang="EN-US">dryer, saving you time and energy when drying your clothes<span xml:lang="EN-US">. </span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">Use color-safe detergent and cold water for every load of colors. With today’s super-efficient detergents and better washing machines, you don’t need hot or even warm water to get clothes clean; cold will work just fine and will reduce the chance of colors fading or bleeding into each other. </span></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><strong><span xml:lang="EN-US">The habitual d<span xml:lang="EN-US">ry<span xml:lang="EN-US"> c<span xml:lang="EN-US">leaner </span></span></span></span></strong></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">Summer is <span xml:lang="EN-US">a busy — and sticky — time, running from <span xml:lang="EN-US">work to <span xml:lang="EN-US">outdoor barbecues<span xml:lang="EN-US"><span xml:lang="EN-US"> during the hottest months of the year<span xml:lang="EN-US">. <span xml:lang="EN-US">And r<span xml:lang="EN-US">efreshing <span xml:lang="EN-US">that summer wardrobe between pool parties <span xml:lang="EN-US">is key to the <span xml:lang="EN-US">hab<span xml:lang="EN-US">itual dry cleaner<span xml:lang="EN-US"> looking and feeling their best<span xml:lang="EN-US">. <span xml:lang="EN-US">That’s where the LG <span xml:lang="EN-US">Styler<span xml:lang="EN-US"> comes in. <span xml:lang="EN-US">The LG <span xml:lang="EN-US">Styler<span xml:lang="EN-US"> is a fashion-forward, one-of-a-kind clothing management system that can refresh and sanitize clothing in as little as 20 minutes. Just get back from an outdoor cocktail party? Simply place your favorite dresses, shirts or suits inside and let LG’s <span xml:lang="EN-US">TrueSteam<span xml:lang="EN-US"><span xml:lang="EN-US"> technology work its magic to reduce wrinkles and odors from things like sweat or smoke, without any harsh chemicals.<span xml:lang="EN-US"> <span xml:lang="EN-US">While it doesn’t replace dry cleaning, it can certainly help reduce trips to the cleaners while keeping your clothes crisp and ready to go before your next brunch date or happy hour. </span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>
<div>
<p><span xml:lang="EN-US">Whatever your laundry personality, you can find a washer, dryer and detergent that will make your chore easier and less time consuming<span xml:lang="EN-US">. <span xml:lang="EN-US">Then, you can spend that time on other things. In fact, Americans <span xml:lang="EN-US">surveyed <span xml:lang="EN-US">say if they could cut their laundry time in half, they’d spend that extra time hanging out with their kids, watching TV or doing other things they enjoy. </span></span></span></span></span></p>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal/11748277-todays-article-is-very-good</id>
    <published>2020-12-14T13:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-05T15:08:52-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal/11748277-todays-article-is-very-good"/>
    <title>Walk your way to healthy</title>
    <author>
      <name>Richard Bairstow</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span>Whether it is bikini season or time to strut your stuff on the streets of New York, there is no reason not to stay healthy. </span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://testament.myshopify.com/pt/blogs/journal/11748277-todays-article-is-very-good">Mais</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><br>Walk your way to healthy<br><br>Whether it is bikini season, time to strut your stuff on the streets of New York or a case of throwing the kids in the car in a desperate bid to make the school run there is no reason not to stay healthy. This doesn't mean all out exercise of finding those non existent hours to hit the gym that others seem to always have however.<br><br>We put together some easy to implement changes to your daily routine that are not life changing but will help you do a little more towards getting back on the road to a healthier lifestyle.<br><br>Walk when you can't run<br>Walking is great for you, it not only keeps your muscles moving but it is a great way to clear your mind and gain some perspective. Consider parking further away from the store when shopping or running errands. Get off the bus or train a stop early on your commute to the office and walk the rest of the way. Invest in a step counter and aim for that elusive 10,000 a day. In no time you will be striving towards that elusive 10 before 10.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
